# **CLAIRE FRANCIS**

Austin, TX 78701 | (817) 350-3315 | clairemfran@gmail.com

## **Professional Summary**

Pre-dental, Biology student passionate about building confidence through autonomy, appearance, and meaningful connection. Bringing three years of experience mentoring young girls, and five years professional experience managing children. In search of employment to utilize skills in childcare, confidence-building, and interpersonal communication.

### **Skills**

- Interpersonal Communication
- Youth Mentorship
- Organization
- Leadership

- Design Skills
- Administration
- Education

## **Work History**

Student Mentor Jan 2018 - Current

Girlstart Austin, TX

Led weekly, after-school program to instill critical thinking and collaboration in 4th and 5th grade girls through hands-on, career oriented STEM activities.

Floater Jan 2020 - Mar 2020

Smile 360 Austin, TX

Supported dental office staff and increased office efficiency through work in sterilization, office innovation research, insurance verification, dental procedure assistance, procedure room set-up and clean-up, and general office sanitation.

Sales Associate Oct 2014 - Aug 2017

Dancer's Closet Arlington, TX

Interacted with young ballerinas and their parents to find ideal products. Processed shipments to complete timely updates of shelves and merchandise displays. Resolved customer complaints with friendly, service-oriented support.

#### Education

Bachelor of Science: Human Biology Expected in May 2021